ANTHONY DOMINGUEZ

• DETAILS •

3970 East Meadow Drive Duluth, GA, 30096 305 336 7224 adominguez11186@gmail.com

• LINKS •

<u>Linked In</u>

Profile

Git Hub

• SKILLS •

Strong Leadership Skills

Programming Languages

Event Management

Ability to Work in a Team

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Multitask

Adaptability

Customer Service

PROFILE

Full stack web developer with previous experience in high stress environments. Recently earned a certificate in full stack web development from Georgia Institute of Technology. Skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with extreme proficiency under challenging situations, ability to meet deadlines, and ability to work and be efficient with a team. With every project my goal is to fully understand the execution of the code for server software and also create a functional and useful tool for the client software. My past experiences and career have shaped me to be a teamplayer in which I applied aspects of UX and agile development in a recent project where I worked in a team of four to develop a single-page app that allows users a way to search items in their area to pick up or post unwanted items.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Executive Sous Chef at Sonesta Gwinnett Place, Duluth, GA

January 2020 — January 2021

Assisted Executive Chef in execution of Food and Beverage for 2 restaurants, 15,000 sq ft banquet facility, and 300 room hotel.

Sous Chef at Dantanna's Surf and Turf, Atlanta, GA

February 2021 — February 2021

Assisted Executive chef in execution of 250 seat restaurant serving lunch, dinner, and late night service.

EDUCATION

Certificate Full Stack Web Development , Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta November 2020 — May 2021

Bachelors of Science: Foodservice Management, Johnson & Wales University August 2008 — February 2012

■ REFERENCES

Dewey Lossaso Corporate Executive Chef

305 610 7477

Amin Noorazi General Manager

305 785 0944

Albert Cabrero General Manager from Advance Auto

786 261 1775